Center for a Woman's Own Name Records
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
Center for a Woman’s Own Name Records 1956-2008 1972-1985
MSS85452
Center for a Woman’s Own Name
4,700 items
18 containers
7 linear feet
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress Washington, D.C.
National non-profit organization. Correspondence, legal records, newspaper clippings, press releases, printed material, and other records documenting the organization’s work as a clearinghouse for information concerning state laws, lawsuits, and various legal and social issues relating to women’s efforts to retain their chosen name after marriage.
Selected Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the LC Catalog. They are grouped by name of person or organization, by subject or location, and by occupation and listed alphabetically.
People
Feigen, Brenda--Correspondence.; Ginsburg, Ruth Bader--Correspondence.; Harney, Kathleen R.--Correspondence.; Kessler, Joan F.--Correspondence.; King, Jean L. (Jean Ledwith)--Correspondence.; Krauss, Elissa--Correspondence.; Landers, Ann--Correspondence.; Levedahl, Kathryn Scates, 1927-2014--Correspondence.; MacDougall, Priscilla Ruth--Correspondence.; MacDougall, Priscilla Ruth.; Mead, Margaret, 1901-1978--Correspondence.; Montage, Judith Natale--Correspondence.; Montandon, Pat--Correspondence.; Peratis, Kathleen Willert--Correspondence.; Roberts, Sylvia--Correspondence.; Sandler, Bernice Resnick--Correspondence.; Sheley, Kathy Ann--Correspondence.; Sousa, Sheila Cabral--Correspondence.; Stannard, Una, 1927-2004--Correspondence.; Takemoto, Anne H.--Correspondence.; Tepper, Terri P.; Tepper, Terri P.--Correspondence.; Tepper, Terri P.--Family--Correspondence.; Van Buren, Abigail, 1918-2013--Correspondence.; Vanderbilt, Amy--Correspondence.; Weddington, Sarah Ragle--Correspondence.
Organizations
American Civil Liberties Union. Women's Rights Project--Correspondence.; Center for a Woman's Own Name.; Consumer Credit Project. Consumer Credit Project records. 1973-1984.; Lucy Stone League--Correspondence.; National Organization for Women--Correspondence.; Olympia Brown League--Correspondence.; Playboy Foundation--Correspondence.; Women's Legal Defense Fund, inc.--Correspondence.
Subjects
Consumer credit--United States.; Credit--United States.; Names, Personal--Law and legislation--United States.; Names, Personal--United States.; Names, Personal.; Sex discrimination against women--United States.; Sex discrimination in consumer credit--United States.; Women's rights--United States.; Women--Finance, Personal--United States.; Women--Taxation--United States.; Women--United States--Economic conditions.; Women--United States--Social conditions.; Women--United States.
Places
United States--Social conditions--20th century.; United States--Social life and customs.
Acquisition Information
The records of the Center for a Woman’s Own Name were given to the Library of Congress by the organization's cofounder and director, Terri P. Tepper, in 2009.
Access and Restrictions
The records of the Center for a Woman's Own Name are open to research. Researchers are advised to contact the Manuscript Reading Room prior to visiting. Many collections are stored off-site and advance notice is needed to retrieve these items for research use.
Organizational History
In 1972, Terri P. Tepper, cofounder and director of the Center for a Woman’s Own Name, petitioned the 19th Judicial Circuit Court of Illinois to change her surname and to recognize Ms. as a legal title. The petition was granted, making Tepper the first woman in Illinois to regain her chosen name after marriage and marking the first time the State of Illinois recognized Ms. as a legally designated title. The material in this collection relates to Tepper's name change petition and the creation of the Center for a Woman’s Own Name and contains only passing references to the legal recognition of Ms.
The Center for a Woman’s Own Name began informally in 1973 when Tepper placed an advertisement in Ms. magazine seeking information on state law and policies relating to women’s names. The Center was incorporated later that year, with Tepper as director and president; Priscilla Ruth MacDougall as director, vice president, and legal consultant; and Diana Altman as director. The Center developed into a clearinghouse for information concerning state laws, lawsuits, and various legal and social issues relating to women’s efforts to retain their chosen name after marriage. The Center did not advocate that women retain their maiden names after marriage; instead, the Center maintained that women had a right to determine their legal name irrespective of their marital status.
Through a network of volunteers, the Center tracked legal opinions and on-going lawsuits on a state-by-state basis. With correspondence from the general public, prominent individuals, national organizations, and government officials, the collection’s strength lies in its ability to document the evolving societal attitudes and legal opinions around the name issue as well as individual and institutional responses to women maintaining their own names after marriage.
Biographical Note
Terri P. Tepper
Date Event
1942, May 29 Born Denver, Colo.
1964 B.S., education, Boston University, Boston, Mass.
1964, Aug. 23 Married Lawrence Jay Weiner
1964 1970 Elementary school teacher, Barrington, Ill. and Chicago, Ill.
1972 In re Weiner
1973 President, National Organization for Women. North Suburban Chicago Chapter, Techny, Ill.
1973 Outstanding Achievement award, National Organization for Women. North Suburban Chicago Chapter, Techny, Ill.
1973 1984 Founder, president, and director, Center for a Woman’s Own Name, Barrington, Ill.
1974 Published with Diana Altman and Priscilla Ruth MacDougall Booklet for Women Who Wish to Determine Their Own Names After Marriage. Center for a Woman’s Own Name: Barrington, Ill.
1976 1984 Founder and director, Consumer Credit Project, Barrington, Ill.
1980 Published with Nona Dawe Tepper, The New Entrepreneurs: Women Working from Home. New York: Universe Books
1981 B.A., photography, Columbia College, Chicago, Ill.
1982 One-woman photography exhibition, Chicago Cultural Center, Chicago, Ill.
1984 1985 President, Illinois Council on Home Based Enterprise
2007 Trainer and owner, The Cultivated Canine, Barrington, Ill.
Scope and Content Note
The records of the Center for a Woman’s Own Name span the years 1956-2008, with the bulk of the material dating from 1972 to 1985. The collection is comprised primarily of correspondence but also includes administrative files, clippings, legal files, promotional materials, and publications. The papers are in English and are organized into the following four series: Correspondence, State File, Consumer Credit Project, and Miscellany.
The Correspondence series documents both public and private reactions to Tepper’s name change petition and her initial efforts to gather information and resources to form the Center. The Tepper's correspondence with her family includes letters between Tepper and her mother-in-law, Idelle Weiner, along with Tepper’s personal narrative detailing the impact Tepper’s name change had on their relationship. The correspondence between Priscilla Ruth MacDougall and Tepper reflects the development of the Center’s mission and strategy as well as MacDougall’s analysis of legal cases and opinions. The series contains both incoming and outgoing correspondence, primarily between MacDougall and Tepper. Notable correspondents in this series include Brenda Feigen, Ruth Bader Ginsburg, Elissa Krauss, and Kathleen Willert Peratis who represent organizations such as the American Civil Liberties Union Women’s Rights Project, the Lucy Stone League, National Organization for Women, and Women’s Legal Defense Fund.
The State File comprises the bulk of the collection and consists primarily of correspondence. The series contains a master file of attorney general opinions and state legislative councils; therein, the series is organized alphabetically by state. The material in this series was used by Tepper to track each state’s recent legal opinions and legislation. The volunteers correspondence contains letters from individuals and organizations that act as contacts in each state. Their duties included providing the Center with updates on state legislation and lawsuits and distributing the Center's fact sheets and informational pamphlets. The material in this series complements the general correspondence from the Correspondence series as many of these individuals and organizations initially contacted Tepper to request information on name change law.
Notable correspondents include Joan F. Kessler, Jean L. King, Ann Landers, Kathryn Scates Levedahl, Pat Montandon, the Olympia Brown League, The Playboy Foundation, Sylvia Roberts, Bernice Sandler, Sheila Cabral Sousa, Una Stannard, Abigail Van Buren, Amy Vanderbilt, and Sarah Ragle Weddington. The series also includes correspondence from name change petitioners Kathleen R. Harney, Judith Natale Montage, and Anne H. Takemoto as well as those who used common law to establish their legal names such as Kathy Ann Sheley.
The State File demonstrates the wide reaching network of individuals and organizations supporting a woman’s right to determine her own name as well as the disagreements among supporters regarding the best method and strategy to ensure this right. The series is especially rich in personal narratives, women expressing the connection between their names and their sense of identity and autonomy. These narratives illustrate the way state laws, institutional policies, bureaucratic barriers, and personal bias impacted women on a practical level, affecting their ability to file tax returns and obtain identification and credit. The realization that many women lost their credit history after they took their husband’s name and were often unable to obtain credit under their own name after marriage led Tepper to create the Consumer Credit Project.
The Consumer Credit Project series contains administrative files, clippings, correspondence, credit discrimination complaints, credit surveys, legal files, promotional materials, publications, and other writings. The series documents the Project’s efforts to educate women about their credit rights and to help those who had faced discriminatory credit practices.
The Miscellany series includes administrative files, announcements, clippings, legal files, promotional material, publications, and a scrapbook. The historical file includes an essay by Tepper chronicling her decision to file the name change petition and the creation of the Center. The legal file consists chiefly of material from Lawrence Jay Weiner, an attorney and Tepper’s husband, who represented Tepper and several other women in their name change petitions. This series also contains MacDougall’s published writings on women and name change law.
Arrangement of the Records
This collection is arranged in four series:
Correspondence, 1972-1985
State File, 1969-1985
Consumer Credit Project, 1973-1984
Miscellany, 1956-2008
Container List
- Correspondence, 1972-1985 (Box 1-2)
  Correspondence with individuals, various federal agencies and armed services, organizations and schools, the press, and Terri P. Tepper's family.
  Arranged alphabetically by topic and name of person or organization and chronologically therein.
  - Federal government (Box 1)
    - Air Force, 1973-1977 (Box 1)
    - Army, 1975-1980 (Box 1)
    - Military, 1974-1977 (Box 1)
    - Navy, 1973-1974 See also Container 9, State File, Texas, Individuals, Sheley, Kathy Ann (Box 1)
    - State Department, 1973-1983 (Box 1)
  - Financial (Box 1)
    - Insurance, 1975 (Box 1)
    - Tax returns, 1972-1975, undated (Box 1)
  - Foreign file (Box 1)
    - Australia - Austria, 1974-1982 (Box 1)
    - Canada, 1976, 1982 (Box 1)
    - Egypt-England, 1973-1982 (Box 1)
    - France-Greece, 1973-1976 (Box 1)
    - Ireland-Israel, 1974-1980 (Box 1)
    - Italy, 1973-1977 (Box 1)
    - Japan-Lebanon, 1974-1975 (Box 1)
    - Morocco, 1974 See also Container 12, State File, Volunteers, Washington, Hankamer, Mary (Box 1)
    - Saudi Arabia-Turkey, 1974-1982 (Box 1)
    - Virgin Islands-West Indies, 1974-1977 (Box 1)
  - General (Box 1)
    - 1972 (Box 1)
    - 1973 (Box 1)
      - Jan.-June (Box 1)
      - July-Dec. (Box 1)
    - 1974 (Box 1)
      - Jan.-May (Box 1)
      - July-Dec. (Box 1)
    - 1975 (Box 1)
    - 1976-1985 (Box 1)
  - Individuals (Box 1)
    - Borowicz, Sue, 1973 (Box 1)
    - Kegan, Esther, 1975 (Box 1)
    - MacDougall, Priscilla Ruth with Terri P. Tepper See also Container 10, State File, Volunteers, California, Montandon, Pat (Box 2)
      - 1973 (Box 2)
        - Feb.-July (Box 2)
        - Aug.-Dec. (Box 2)
      - 1974 (Box 2)
        - Jan.-July (Box 2)
        - Aug.-Dec. (Box 2)
      - 1975 (Box 2)
    - Nickless, Pam, 1973 (Box 2)
    - Tepper, Terri P. and family, 1972-1976 (Box 2)
  - Opposition (Box 2)
    - Crank, 1974-1976 (Box 2)
    - Disapproving, 1972-1974 (Box 2)
  - Organizations and schools (Box 2)
    - American Civil Liberties Union. Women's Rights Project, New York, N.Y., 1972-1974 (Box 2)
    - Citizens' Advisory Council on the Status of Women (U.S.), 1974 (Box 2)
    - Federation of Organizations for Professional Women (U.S.), 1974-1975 (Box 2)
    - Lucy Stone League, New York, N.Y., 1973-1974 (Box 2)
    - National Organization for Women New York, N.Y., 1973-1975 (Box 2)
    - NOW Legal Defense & Education Fund, New York, N.Y., 1973-1974 (Box 2)
    - Universities, 1973-1978 (Box 2)
    - Various, 1973-1975 (Box 2)
    - Women's Legal Defense Fund, Inc., Washington, D.C., 1973-1975 (Box 2)
  - Press (Box 2)
    - General (Box 2)
      - 1973-1975 (Box 2)
      - 1976-1984 (Box 2)
    - Today Publications and News Service, Inc., 1974 (Box 2)
    - Editorial corrections, 1973-1975 (Box 2)
- State File, 1969-1985 (Box 3-12)
  Correspondence with attorneys general, legislative councils, individuals, litigants, organizations and schools, press, and volunteers.
  Grouped into administrative, general, and volunteer files. Arranged therein alphabetically by state and type of material.
  - Administrative file (Box 3)
    - Attorneys general, 1972-1975 (Box 3)
      - Alabama-Connecticut (Box 3)
      - Delaware-Louisiana (Box 3)
      - Maryland-Virginia (Box 3)
    - Legislative file, Arizona-Wyoming, 1969-1974 (Box 3)
    - Subject file, driver's licenses, 1974-1975 (Box 3)
  - General (Box 3)
    - Alabama (Box 3)
      - Attorney general, 1983 (Box 3)
      - General correspondence, 1975-1983 (Box 3)
      - Litigation, 1972-1973 (Box 3)
      - Subject file, children's names, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
    - Alaska (Box 3)
      - Attorney general, 1976-1983 (Box 3)
      - General correspondence, 1979-1983 (Box 3)
      - Litigation, 1974 (Box 3)
    - Arizona (Box 3)
      - Attorney general, 1975-1980 (Box 3)
      - General correspondence, 1975-1983 (Box 3)
    - Arkansas (Box 3)
      - Attorney general, 1974 (Box 3)
      - Legislative file, 1983 (Box 3)
    - California (Box 3)
      - Attorney general, 1974-1893 (Box 3)
      - General correspondence (Box 3)
        - 1979-1982 (Box 3)
        - 1983-1984 (Box 3)
      - Legislative file, 1974, undated (Box 3)
      - Organizations and schools (Box 3)
        - The Playboy Foundation, Chicago, Ill. (Box 3)
          - General correspondence, 1975-1983 (Box 3)
          - Public response to advertising and articles in Playboy Magazine (Box 3)
            - 1979 (Box 3)
            - 1980-1983 (Box 3)
        - Various, 1973-1974 (Box 3)
      - Press, 1974-1982 (Box 3)
      - Subject file (Box 3)
        - Children's names, 1977-1978 (Box 3)
        - Credit, 1973-1983 (Box 3)
        - Passports, 1978 (Box 3)
    - Colorado (Box 3)
      - Attorney general, 1983 (Box 3)
      - General correspondence, 1980-1983 (Box 3)
      - Legislative file, 1983 (Box 3)
    - Connecticut (Box 3)
      - Attorney general, 1983 (Box 3)
      - General correspondence, 1974-1981 (Box 3)
      - Legislative file, 1983 (Box 3)
      - Subject file, passports, 1973-1974 (Box 3)
    - Delaware, attorney general, 1983 (Box 4)
    - District of Columbia (Box 4)
      - Attorney general, 1983 (Box 4)
      - General correspondence, 1974-1983 (Box 4)
      - Legislative file, 1974 (Box 4)
      - Litigation, In re Barringham, 1978 (Box 4)
      - Press, 1975-1982, undated (Box 4)
    - Florida (Box 4)
      - Attorney general, 1976-1983 (Box 4)
      - General correspondence, 1974-1983 (Box 4)
      - Legislative file, 1974-1983 (Box 4)
      - Litigation, 1974-1983 (Box 4)
      - Organizations and schools, 1974-1981 (Box 4)
    - Georgia (Box 4)
      - Attorney general, 1974-1983 (Box 4)
      - General correspondence, 1974-1983 (Box 4)
      - Legislative file, 1982 (Box 4)
      - Organizations and schools, 1973-1975 (Box 4)
      - Press, 1974, 1982 (Box 4)
    - Hawaii (Box 4)
      - Attorney general, 1973-1983 (Box 4)
      - General correspondence, 1974-1981 (Box 4)
      - Individuals (Box 4)
        - Haley, Allan S., 1973-1974 (Box 4)
        - Takemoto, Anne H., 1973-1982 (Box 4)
      - Legislative file, 1974, 1982 (Box 4)
      - Subject file (Box 4)
        - Banking and credit, 1974-1975 (Box 4)
        - Children's names, 1977-1979 (Box 4)
    - Idaho (Box 4)
      - Attorney general, 1983 (Box 4)
      - General correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box 4)
    - Illinois (Box 4)
      - Attorney general, 1974-1982 (Box 4)
      - Attorneys, 1973-1978 (Box 4)
      - General correspondence (Box 4)
        - 1974-1977 (Box 4)
        - 1978-1982 (Box 4)
        - 1983-1985 (Box 4)
      - Individuals (Box 5)
        - Dye, Ellen, 1974 (Box 5)
        - Ecko, Bev, 1974-1976 (Box 5)
        - Fowke, Barbara, 1973-1974 (Box 5)
        - Jaspers, Mary, 1973-1974 (Box 5)
        - Landers, Ann, 1974-1980, undated (Box 5)
        - Loonin, Flory, 1973 (Box 5)
        - MacDougall, Curtis D., 1973-1974 (Box 5)
        - MacDougall, Genevieve R., 1974 (Box 5)
        - McGrady, Charlene Ann, 1974-1976 (Box 5)
        - Rosenberg, Lory D., 1973 (Box 5)
        - Stanford, Catherine M., 1974 (Box 5)
        - Tschannen-Moran, Bob, 1976 (Box 5)
        - Van Buren, Abigail, 1980-1981 (Box 5)
        - Various, 1974-1975 (Box 5)
      - Legislative file, 1975-1982 (Box 5)
      - Organizations and schools (Box 5)
        - Illinois. Commission on the Status of Women, Springfield, Ill., 1976-1983 (Box 5)
        - Illinois Humanities Council, Barrington, Ill., 1975 (Box 5)
        - Midwest Women's Center, Chicago, Ill., 1983 (Box 5)
        - National Organization for Women, Chicago, Ill., 1974-1976 (Box 5)
        - Universities, 1974-1983 (Box 5)
        - Various, 1974-1983 (Box 5)
        - Women's groups, 1973-1978, undated (Box 5)
      - Press (Box 5)
        - Clippings, 1972-1984, undated (Box 5)
        - General correspondence, 1974-1982 (Box 5)
        - Public response to advertising and articles in media, 1974-1983 (Box 5)
      - Secretary of state, 1973-1975 (Box 5)
      - Subject file (Box 5)
        - Banking and credit, 1973-1974 (Box 5)
        - Bookstores, 1974 (Box 5)
        - Employment, 1975 (Box 5)
        - Medical records, 1974-1975 (Box 5)
        - Voting, 1976-1977 (Box 5)
    - Indiana (Box 5)
      - General correspondence, 1980-1982 (Box 5)
      - Individuals (Box 5)
        - Lamber, Julia C., 1973-1974 (Box 5)
        - Shula, Robert J., 1973-1974 See also Container 5, State File, Indiana, Litigation, In re Hauptly (Box 5)
      - Legislative file, 1983 (Box 5)
      - Litigation, In re Hauptly, 1974 See also Container 5, State File, Indiana, Individuals, Shula, Robert J. (Box 5)
    - Iowa (Box 5)
      - Attorney general, 1982 (Box 5)
      - General correspondence, 1973-1978 (Box 5)
      - Individuals, Zazubek, Carole, 1973 (Box 5)
    - Kansas (Box 6)
      - Attorney general, 1983 (Box 6)
      - General correspondence, 1973-1983 (Box 6)
      - Individuals, Wheeler, Louise A., 1973-1974 (Box 6)
    - Kentucky (Box 6)
      - Attorney general, 1972-1983 (Box 6)
      - General correspondence, 1974-1983 (Box 6)
      - Individuals (Box 6)
        - Elam, Pam, 1977-1978 (Box 6)
        - Flannery, Maureen A., 1981-1983 (Box 6)
      - Legislative file, 1974-1983 (Box 6)
      - Litigation, Sylvia Scott Whitlow v. F. E. Hodges, 1974 (Box 6)
    - Louisiana (Box 6)
      - Attorney general, 1982-1983 (Box 6)
      - Individuals, Roberts, Sylvia, 1973 (Box 6)
    - Maine (Box 6)
      - Attorney general, 1974-1983 (Box 6)
      - General correspondence, 1973-1983 (Box 6)
      - Individuals, Herman, Mary, 1973-1976 (Box 6)
    - Maryland (Box 6)
      - Attorney general, 1972-1983 (Box 6)
      - General correspondence, 1973-1983 (Box 6)
      - Individuals (Box 6)
        - Drudge, Deborah, 1974 (Box 6)
        - Fuller, Mary, 1973 (Box 6)
        - Levedahl, Kathryn Scates, 1973-1974 (Box 6)
      - Legislative file, 1981-1983 (Box 6)
      - Organizations and schools, Women's Law Center, 1973 (Box 6)
    - Massachusetts (Box 6)
      - Attorney general, 1977-1983 (Box 6)
      - General correspondence, 1973-1983 (Box 6)
      - Legislative file, 1973-1983 (Box 6)
      - Press, 1974-1983 (Box 6)
    - Michigan (Box 6)
      - Attorney general, 1980-1983 (Box 6)
      - Attorneys, 1974-1982 (Box 6)
      - General correspondence, 1974-1984 (Box 6)
      - Individuals (Box 6)
        - Kennedy, Alexandra Eva, 1974-1976 (Box 6)
        - King, Jean L., 1973-1979 (Box 6)
        - Solvenko, Ralph, 1982 (Box 6)
        - Wyss, Kathy, 1974 (Box 6)
      - Legislative file, 1974-1983 (Box 7)
      - Organizations and schools, 1973-1979 (Box 7)
      - Press, 1974-1983 (Box 7)
      - Secretary of state, 1975 (Box 7)
    - Minnesota (Box 7)
      - General correspondence, 1973-1983 (Box 7)
      - Individuals (Box 7)
        - Hoium, Cheryl A., 1974 (Box 7)
        - Wille, Karen L., 1974 (Box 7)
      - Legislative file, 1983 (Box 7)
      - Minnesota Civil Liberties Union, Minneapolis, Minn., 1973 (Box 7)
    - Mississippi (Box 7)
      - General correspondence, 1973-1974, 1983 (Box 7)
      - Legislative file, 1983 (Box 7)
      - Organizations and schools, 1973, 1980 (Box 7)
    - Missouri (Box 7)
      - Attorney general, 1983 (Box 7)
      - Attorneys, 1974, 1983 (Box 7)
      - General correspondence, 1973-1983 (Box 7)
      - Individuals (Box 7)
        - Achtenberg, David, 1973-1974 (Box 7)
        - Frehes, Maryann, 1973-1974 (Box 7)
        - Montage, Judith Natale, 1973-1975 (Box 7)
        - Sussman, Frank, 1973-1974 (Box 7)
        - West, Patricia Ann, 1974 (Box 7)
    - Montana (Box 7)
      - Attorney general, 1983 (Box 7)
      - Individuals, Weiner Kayla Lee, 1974-1976 (Box 7)
      - Legislative file, 1983-1984 (Box 7)
    - Nebraska (Box 7)
      - Attorney general, 1983 (Box 7)
      - General correspondence, 1973-1985 (Box 7)
      - Individuals (Box 7)
        - Tewhill, Kathleen, 1974 (Box 7)
        - Trombley, Ann, 1973 (Box 7)
        - Williams, Patricia K., 1979-1983 (Box 7)
    - Legislative file, 1983 (Box 7)
    - Organizations and schools (Box 7)
      - Nebraska Commission on the Status of Women, Lincoln, Neb., 1977-1979 (Box 7)
      - Universities, 1976-1983 (Box 7)
    - Nevada (Box 7)
      - Individuals, Fancher, Christine, 1974-1978 (Box 7)
      - Legislative file, 1982 (Box 7)
    - New Hampshire (Box 7)
      - Attorney general, 1975, 1983 (Box 7)
      - General correspondence, 1973-1981 (Box 7)
      - Legislative file, 1983 (Box 7)
    - New Jersey (Box 7)
      - Attorney general, 1975 (Box 7)
      - General correspondence (Box 7)
        - 1975-1982 (Box 7)
        - 1983-1984 (Box 7)
      - Legislative file, 1974, 1983 (Box 7)
      - Subject file, driver's licenses, 1978-1982 (Box 7)